<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>1.15</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
<Company_Info>
        <Company_Name>Rudolph Loew</Company_Name>
        <Address_1>506 Bieling Rd.</Address_1>
        <Address_2 />
        <City_Town>Elmont</City_Town>
        <State_Province>NY</State_Province>
        <Zip_Postal_Code>11003</Zip_Postal_Code>
        <Country>USA</Country>
        <Company_WebSite_URL>http://members.aol.com/rloew1</Company_WebSite_URL>
<Contact_Info>
        <Author_First_Name>Rudolph</Author_First_Name>
        <Author_Last_Name>Loew</Author_Last_Name>
        <Author_Email>rloew@hotmail.com</Author_Email>
        <Contact_First_Name>Rudolph</Contact_First_Name>
        <Contact_Last_Name>Loew</Contact_Last_Name>
        <Contact_Email>rloew@hotmail.com</Contact_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
<Support_Info>
        <Sales_Email>rloew@hotmail.com</Sales_Email>
        <Support_Email>rloew@hotmail.com</Support_Email>
        <General_Email>rloew@hotmail.com</General_Email>
        <Sales_Phone>516-352-9078</Sales_Phone>
        <Support_Phone>516-352-9078</Support_Phone>
        <General_Phone>516-352-9078</General_Phone>
        <Fax_Phone>516-352-9078</Fax_Phone>
    </Support_Info>
</Company_Info>
<Program_Info>
        <Program_Name>High Capacity Disk Patch</Program_Name>
        <Program_Version>4.5</Program_Version>
        <Program_Release_Month>09</Program_Release_Month>
        <Program_Release_Day>16</Program_Release_Day>
        <Program_Release_Year>2005</Program_Release_Year>
        <Program_Cost_Dollars>10.00</Program_Cost_Dollars>
        <Program_Cost_Other_Code />
        <Program_Cost_Other />
        <Program_Type>Demo</Program_Type>
        <Program_Release_Status>Minor Update</Program_Release_Status>
        <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
        <Program_OS_Support>Win98,WinME</Program_OS_Support>
        <Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
<File_Info>
        <Filename_Versioned>PATCHE01.ZIP</Filename_Versioned>
        <Filename_Previous />
        <Filename_Generic>PATCHE.ZIP</Filename_Generic>
        <Filename_Long />
        <File_Size_Bytes>42540</File_Size_Bytes>
        <File_Size_K>42</File_Size_K>
        <File_Size_MB>0.041</File_Size_MB>
    </File_Info>
<Expire_Info>
        <Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
        <Expire_Count />
        <Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
        <Expire_Other_Info />
        <Expire_Month />
        <Expire_Day />
        <Expire_Year />
    </Expire_Info>
        <Program_Change_Info>Updated Manual</Program_Change_Info>
        <Program_Specific_Category>Utilities</Program_Specific_Category>
        <Program_Categories>System Patches, Disk Drivers</Program_Categories>
        <Program_System_Requirements>Windows 98/SE/ME, 48 Bit IDE Aware BIOS</Program_System_Requirements>
        <Includes_JAVA_VM>N</Includes_JAVA_VM>
        <Includes_VB_Runtime>N</Includes_VB_Runtime>
        <Includes_DirectX>N</Includes_DirectX>
</Program_Info>
<Program_Descriptions>
<English>
        <Keywords>System Patch,  Driver Patch, 137GB, 128GB, ATA-6, 48-Bit LBA, ESDI_506.PDR, Large Hard Drives</Keywords>
        <Char_Desc_45>Patch for Windows to support &gt;137GB Drives</Char_Desc_45>
        <Char_Desc_80>This Program patches Windows 98/98SE/ME to support Drives Larger Than 137GB</Char_Desc_80>
        <Char_Desc_250>The High Capacity Disk Patch Program patches Windows 98/98SE/ME to provide
direct support for hard drives larger than 137GB without requiring a
controller card or the Intel Application Accelerator.</Char_Desc_250>
        <Char_Desc_450>The High Capacity Disk Patch Program patches Windows 98/98SE/ME to provide
direct support for hard drives larger than 137GB without requiring a
controller card or the Intel Application Accelerator which can only be
used with an Intel chipset motherboard. The patch installs support for the
48-Bit addressing mode required for hard drives larger than 137GB.</Char_Desc_450>
        <Char_Desc_2000>The High Capacity Disk Patch Program patches Windows 98/98SE/ME to provide
direct support for hard drives larger than 137GB without requiring a
controller card or the Intel Application Accelerator which can only be
used with an Intel chipset motherboard. The patch installs support for the
48-Bit addressing mode required for hard drives larger than 137GB.</Char_Desc_2000>
</English>
</Program_Descriptions>
<Web_Info>
<Application_URLs>
        <Application_Info_URL>http://members.aol.com/rloew1/Programs/PatchE01.htm</Application_Info_URL>
        <Application_Order_URL />
        <Application_Screenshot_URL>http://members.aol.com/rloew1/Programs/Patch137.jpg</Application_Screenshot_URL>
        <Application_Icon_URL />
        <Application_XML_File_URL>http://members.aol.com/rloew1/Programs/Patch137.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
<Download_URLs>
        <Primary_Download_URL>http://members.aol.com/rloew1/Programs/Patch137.zip</Primary_Download_URL>
        <Secondary_Download_URL />
        <Additional_Download_URL_1 />
        <Additional_Download_URL_2 />
    </Download_URLs>
</Web_Info>
<Permissions>
        <Distribution_Permissions />
        <EULA>High Capacity Disk Patch

Copyright (C) 2003-2005
by Rudolph R. Loew
All Rights Reserved.


License Agreement 

LICENSE: Rudolph Loew grants you a nonexclusive license to use the 
accompanying copyrighted software program(s) (the &quot;SOFTWARE&quot;), which 
includes any associated software components, and any online or electronic 
documentation, subject to the terms and restrictions set forth in this 
License Agreement. By installing, copying, or otherwise using the 
SOFTWARE, you agree to be bound by the terms of this License Agreement. 

This software is licensed to you free for your evaluation. This Demo software
is limited to 145GB. Reading and/or Writing data above this limit is likely
to cause corruption and data loss. You are solely responsible for any
damages caused by exceeding this limit. To use more than 145GB you must
purchase the full version of this software.

Copies of the program may be copied and distributed freely provided that
all files are copied and distributed together including all Copyright
Notices and this License Agreement.

You are not permitted to lease, rent, or sublicense the Software, use the
Software after the expiration of your License or on more Computers than
allowed by your license, or in any other unauthorized manner. Further, no
license is granted to you in the human readable code of the Software
(source code). Except as provided below, this License Agreement does not
grant you any rights to patents, copyrights, trade secrets, trademarks,
or any other rights in respect to the Software.

RESTRICTIONS: Modification, reverse engineering, reverse compiling, or 
disassembly of the SOFTWARE is expressly prohibited, except and only to 
the extent that such activity is expressly permitted by applicable law. 

WARNING:

THIS DEMO VERSION MUST NOT BE USED TO READ OR WRITE DATA ABOVE 145GB, OR IN
A COMPUTER CONTAINING PARTITIONS THAT EXTEND BEYOND 145GB, AS CORRUPTION
WILL OCCUR.

THE POTENTIAL EXISTS FOR DATA LOSS TO OCCUR DUE TO ERRORS IN THE PATCH OR
IF THE PATCHED DRIVER IS BYPASSED OR OVERWRITTEN. DO NOT USE IN CRITICAL
SYSTEMS OR WHERE HUMAN SAFETY IS INVOLVED.

NO WARRANTY: THE SOFTWARE AND DOCUMENTATION ARE PROVIDED ON AN &quot;AS IS&quot;
BASIS AND ALL RISK IS WITH YOU. BECAUSE THE SOFTWARE AND DOCUMENTATION 
ARE PROVIDED TO YOU FREE OF CHARGE, RUDOLPH LOEW MAKES NO WARRANTIES, 
EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, AS TO ANY MATTER WHATSOEVER. IN 
PARTICULAR, ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A 
PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTIES RIGHTS ARE 
EXPRESSLY EXCLUDED. FURTHER, RUDOLPH LOEW MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR 
WARRANTIES THAT THE SOFTWARE AND DOCUMENTATION PROVIDED ARE FREE OF 
ERRORS OR VIRUSES OR THAT THE SOFTWARE AND DOCUMENTATION ARE SUITABLE FOR 
YOUR INTENDED USE. 

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY: IN NO EVENT SHALL RUDOLPH LOEW OR HIS SUPPLIERS 
BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY OTHER PARTY FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR 
CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, LOSS OF DATA OR DATA BEING RENDERED INACCURATE, 
LOSS OF PROFITS OR REVENUE, OR INTERRUPTION OF BUSINESS IN ANY WAY 
ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE SOFTWARE 
AND/OR DOCUMENTATION, REGARDLESS OF THE FORM OF ACTION, WHETHER IN 
CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), STRICT PRODUCT LIABILITY OR 
OTHERWISE, EVEN IF ANY REPRESENTATIVE OF RUDOLPH LOEW OR HIS SUPPLIERS 
HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THIS DISCLAIMER OF 
LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES WILL NOT BE AFFECTED BY ANY FAILURE OF THE SOLE AND 
EXCLUSIVE REMEDIES HEREUNDER. 

EXPORT RULES: You agree that the Software will not be shipped, transferred
or exported into any country or used in any manner prohibited by the United
States Export Administration Act or any other export laws, restrictions or
regulations (collectively the &quot;Export Laws&quot;). In addition, if the Software
is identified as export controlled items under the Export Laws, you
represent and warrant that you are not a citizen, or otherwise located
within, an embargoed nation (including without limitation Iran, Iraq, Syria,
Sudan, Libya, Cuba, North Korea, and Serbia) and that you are not otherwise
prohibited under the Export Laws from receiving the Software. All rights to
Use the Software are granted on condition that such rights are forfeited if
you fail to comply with the terms of this Agreement.

GOVERNING LAW: This Agreement will be governed by and construed in accordance
with the laws in force of the State of New York. The respective courts of
Nassau County, New York shall have jurisdiction over all disputes relating
to this Agreement.

GENERAL PROVISIONS. If any part of this Agreement is found void and
unenforceable, it will not affect the validity of the balance of the
Agreement, which shall remain valid and enforceable according to its terms.
This Agreement shall not prejudice the statutory rights of any party dealing
as a consumer. This Agreement may only be modified by a writing signed by
Rudolph Loew. Updates may be licensed to you by Rudolph Loew with additional
or different terms. This is the entire agreement between Rudolph Loew and
you relating to the Software and it supersedes any prior representations,
discussions, undertakings, communications or advertising relating to the
Software.

Compliance with Licenses. If you are a business or organization, you agree
that upon request from Rudolph Loew or his authorised representative, you
will within thirty (30) days fully document and certify that use of any and
all Software at the time of the request is in conformity with your valid
licenses from Rudolph Loew.

Should you have any questions concerning this License Agreement, or if
you desire to contact Rudolph Loew for any reason, please contact 
Rudolph Loew by electronic mail at: rloew@hotmail.com.</EULA>
</Permissions>
<Simtel>
    <Simtel_Agent />
    <Simtel_FORM>Y</Simtel_FORM>
    <Simtel_DOS_Category>Select - MS-DOS Platform (blank)</Simtel_DOS_Category>
    <Simtel_Platform>win95 - Win95/Win98/WinME</Simtel_Platform>
    <Simtel_Category>Utilities/Drivers/Systems Files - diskmisc Drive / Disc Misc. Utilities</Simtel_Category>
    <SIMTEL_FORM_VER>1.7 03/25/2003</SIMTEL_FORM_VER>
</Simtel>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
